Farewell, Earth
The ship that is departing is
The Space Battleship
Yamato
It departs now to Iscandar,
at the end of the cosmos,
bearing its fate.
"We will come back, no matter what it takes"
Answer with a smile to the waving people
Going far from the Galaxy towards Iscandar
A faint gleam of hope
The Space Battleship Yamato
<Unidentified Czvarke!>
<What is your squad!?>
<Watch your formation!>
<We're in the midst of a review!>
minutes
<This is the patrol squad.>
<We are in pursuit of a suspicious, unidentified craft.>
<Understood. Permission to fire granted.>
Episode 18
Over the Black Light
No matter how steep or far the road is
I will not give up
Endless tears flowing down my cheek are not
A white flag of surrender
I go and become the wings of a loved one
Gather up the shattered dream
And take it to the end of the universe
Steady as she goes!
Row strongly
And hold your thoughts close to your chest
Steady as she goes!
Through your despair
A ray of light shines